<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">SMS Quotes Sender</string>
    <string name="send_lbl_phone">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="send_btn_send">Send</string>
    <string name="schedule_btn_send">Schedule</string>
    <string name="land_loading_txt">Pendind Cetegory Selection</string>

    <!-- DataBase -->

    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>Friendship</item>
        <item>Motivation</item>
        <item>Success</item>
        <item>Positive</item>
        <item>Leadership</item>
        <item>Life</item>
        <item>Education</item>
        <item>Smile</item>
        <item>Wisdom</item>
        <item>Change</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Friendship">
        <item>The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it</item>
        <item>Walking with a friend in the dark is better than walking alone in the light</item>
        <item>A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out</item>
        <item>I cannot even imagine where I would be today were it not for that handful of friends who have given me a heart full of joy. Let\'s face it, friends make life a lot more fun</item>
        <item>Friendship&#8230; is not something you learn in school. But if you haven\'t learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven\'t learned anything.</item>
        <item>It is one of the blessings of old friends that you can afford to be stupid with them</item>
        <item>Sometimes being a friend means mastering the art of timing. There is a time for silence. A time to let go and allow people to hurl themselves into their own destiny. And a time to prepare to pick up the pieces when it\'s all over</item>
        <item>Friends show their love in times of trouble, not in happiness</item>
        <item>Love is the only force capable of transforming an enemy into friend</item>
        <item>One of the most beautiful qualities of true friendship is to understand and to be understood</item>
        <item>The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it</item>
        <item>It is one of the blessings of old friends that you can afford to be stupid with them</item>
        <item>Sometimes being a friend means mastering the art of timing. There is a time for silence. A time to let go and allow people to hurl themselves into their own destiny. And a time to prepare to pick up the pieces when it\'s all over</item>
        <item>Friends show their love in times of trouble, not in happiness</item>
        <item>Love is the only force capable of transforming an enemy into friend</item>
        <item>A single rose can be my garden&#8230; a single friend, my world</item>
        <item>Don\'t walk behind me; I may not lead. Don\'t walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend</item>
        <item>There is nothing on this earth more to be prized than true friendship</item>
        <item>When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives means the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand.</item>
        <item>One loyal friend is worth ten thousand relatives</item>
        <item>In the sweetness of friendship let there be laughter, and sharing of pleasures. For in the dew of little things the heart finds its morning and is refreshed</item>
        <item>A friend is one who knows you and loves you just the same.</item>
        <item>Friendship is one mind in two bodies</item>
        <item>Friends are born, not made.</item>
        <item>My best friend is the one who brings out the best in me</item>
        <item>A friend is someone who gives you total freedom to be yourself</item>
        <item>A true friend freely, advises justly, assists readily, adventures boldly, takes all patiently, defends courageously, and continues a friend unchangeably</item>
        <item>Let us be grateful to people who make us happy, they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom</item>
        <item>My best friend is the man who in wishing me well wishes it for my sake</item>
        <item>Friendship is unnecessary, like philosophy, like art&#8230; It has no survival value; rather it is one of those things that give value to survival</item>
        <item>In everyone\'s life, at some time, our inner fire goes out. It is then burst into flame by an encounter with another human being. We should all be thankful for those people who rekindle the inner spirit</item>
        <item>The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing&#8230; not healing, not curing&#8230; that is a friend who cares</item>
        <item>The language of friendship is not words but meanings.</item>
        <item>Things are never quite as scary when you\'ve got a best friend</item>
        <item>A true friend is someone who is there for you when he\'d rather be anywhere else</item>
        <item>Friends and good manners will carry you where money won\'t go</item>
        <item>The friend in my adversity I shall always cherish most. I can better trust those who helped to relieve the gloom of my dark hours than those who are so ready to enjoy with me the sunshine of my prosperity</item>
        <item>Each friend represents a world in us, a world not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born</item>
        <item>There is a magnet in your heart that will attract true friends. That magnet is unselfishness, thinking of others first; when you learn to live for others, they will live for you</item>
        <item>The best time to make friends is before you need them</item>
        <item>Nothing but heaven itself is better than a friend who is really a friend</item>
        <item>Instead of loving your enemies - treat your friends a little better</item>
        <item>Laughter is not at all a bad beginning for a friendship, and it is far the best ending for one.</item>
        <item>Lots of people want to ride with you in the limo, but what you want is someone who will take the bus with you when the limo breaks down</item>
        <item>Where would you be without friends? The people to pick you up when you need lifting? We come from homes far from perfect, so you end up almost parent and sibling to your friends - your own chosen family. There\'s nothing like a really loyal, dependable, good friend. Nothing</item>
        <item>It is only the great hearted who can be true friends. The mean and cowardly, Can never know what true friendship means</item>
        <item>Since there is nothing so well worth having as friends, never lose a chance to make them</item>
        <item>A true friend is one who overlooks your failures and tolerates your success</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Motivation">
        <item>Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better</item>
        <item>Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time.</item>
        <item>Never give up, for that is just the place and time that the tide will turn.</item>
        <item>Always do your best. What you plant now, you will harvest later.</item>
        <item>Keep your eyes on the stars, and your feet on the ground</item>
        <item>The will to win, the desire to succeed, the urge to reach your full potential&#8230; these are the keys that will unlock the door to personal excellence</item>
        <item>If you can dream it, you can do it</item>
        <item>The secret of getting ahead is getting started</item>
        <item>You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else</item>
        <item>Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better.</item>
        <item>Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time</item>
        <item>The will to win, the desire to succeed, the urge to reach your full potential&#8230; these are the keys that will unlock the door to personal excellence..</item>
        <item>You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else.</item>
        <item>Infuse your life with action. Don\'t wait for it to happen. Make it happen. Make your own future. Make your own hope. Make your own love. And whatever your beliefs, honor your creator, not by passively waiting for grace to come down from upon high, but by doing what you can to make grace happen&#8230; yourself, right now, right down here on Earth.</item>
        <item>Believe in yourself! Have faith in your abilities! Without a humble but reasonable confidence in your own powers you cannot be successful or happy</item>
        <item>In order to succeed, we must first believe that we can</item>
        <item>The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power</item>
        <item>The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it</item>
        <item>With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts</item>
        <item>A creative man is motivated by the desire to achieve, not by the desire to beat others</item>
        <item>Expect problems and eat them for breakfast</item>
        <item>Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can.</item>
        <item>Problems are not stop signs, they are guidelines.</item>
        <item>Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does</item>
        <item>What you get by achieving your goals is not as important as what you become by achieving your goals.</item>
        <item>Do you want to know who you are? Don\'t ask. Act! Action will delineate and define you</item>
        <item>Even if you fall on your face, you\'re still moving forward</item>
        <item>Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence.</item>
        <item>The key is to keep company only with people who uplift you, whose presence calls forth your best</item>
        <item>I don\'t believe you have to be better than everybody else. I believe you have to be better than you ever thought you could be</item>
        <item>Do the difficult things while they are easy and do the great things while they are small. A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step</item>
        <item>Consult not your fears but your hopes and your dreams. Think not about your frustrations, but about your unfulfilled potential. Concern yourself not with what you tried and failed in, but with what it is still possible for you to do.</item>
        <item>Without hard work, nothing grows but weeds.</item>
        <item>Change your life today. Don\'t gamble on the future, act now, without delay.</item>
        <item>Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible</item>
        <item>It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.</item>
        <item>I know where I\'m going and I know the truth, and I don\'t have to be what you want me to be. I\'m free to be what I want</item>
        <item>We are taught you must blame your father, your sisters, your brothers, the school, the teachers - but never blame yourself. It\'s never your fault. But it\'s always your fault, because if you wanted to change you\'re the one who has got to change</item>
        <item>Pursue one great decisive aim with force and determination</item>
        <item>Things do not happen. Things are made to happen</item>
        <item>The harder the conflict, the more glorious the triumph</item>
        <item>You are not here merely to make a living. You are here in order to enable the world to live more amply, with greater vision, with a finer spirit of hope and achievement. You are here to enrich the world, and you impoverish yourself if you forget the errand.</item>
        <item>The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it</item>
        <item>If you\'re going through hell, keep going</item>
        <item>Perseverance is not a long race; it is many short races one after the other.</item>
        <item>Quality is not an act, it is a habit.</item>
        <item>Aim for the moon. If you miss, you may hit a star</item>
        <item>Do something wonderful, people may imitate it</item>
        <item>Do the one thing you think you cannot do. Fail at it. Try again. Do better the second time. The only people who never tumble are those who never mount the high wire. This is your moment. Own it.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Success">
        <item>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts</item>
        <item>The price of success is hard work, dedication to the job at hand, and the determination that whether we win or lose, we have applied the best of ourselves to the task at hand</item>
        <item>To succeed in life, you need two things: ignorance and confidence</item>
        <item>Always be yourself, express yourself, have faith in yourself, do not go out and look for a successful personality and duplicate it</item>
        <item>Try not to become a man of success, but rather try to become a man of value</item>
        <item>Success consists of going from failure to failure without loss of enthusiasm</item>
        <item>Don\'t aim for success if you want it; just do what you love and believe in, and it will come naturally</item>
        <item>The starting point of all achievement is desire</item>
        <item>A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him</item>
        <item>Take up one idea. Make that one idea your life - think of it, dream of it, live on that idea. Let the brain, muscles, nerves, every part of your body, be full of that idea, and just leave every other idea alone. This is the way to success.</item>
        <item>I\'ve failed over and over and over again in my life and that is why I succeed</item>
        <item>In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure.</item>
        <item>I don\'t measure a man\'s success by how high he climbs but how high he bounces when he hits bottom.</item>
        <item>The difference between a successful person and others is not a lack of strength, not a lack of knowledge, but rather a lack of will</item>
        <item>If everyone is moving forward together, then success takes care of itself</item>
        <item>Think twice before you speak, because your words and influence will plant the seed of either success or failure in the mind of another</item>
        <item>No man succeeds without a good woman behind him. Wife or mother, if it is both, he is twice blessed indeed</item>
        <item>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value</item>
        <item>Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune</item>
        <item>Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome</item>
        <item>Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome</item>
        <item>Happiness lies in the joy of achievement and the thrill of creative effort</item>
        <item>There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way</item>
        <item>Eighty percent of success is showing up</item>
        <item>There is little success where there is little laughter</item>
        <item>What\'s money? A man is a success if he gets up in the morning and goes to bed at night and in between does what he wants to do</item>
        <item>The successful man will profit from his mistakes and try again in a different way</item>
        <item>Winning isn\'t everything, it\'s the only thing</item>
        <item>Man needs his difficulties because they are necessary to enjoy success</item>
        <item>Success isn\'t measured by money or power or social rank. Success is measured by your discipline and inner peace.</item>
        <item>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts</item>
        <item>If you have no critics you\'ll likely have no success</item>
        <item>If you wish to succeed in life, make perseverance your bosom friend, experience your wise counselor, caution your elder brother, and hope your guardian genius</item>
        <item>ormula for success: rise early, work hard, strike oil</item>
        <item>The secret of my success is a two word answer: Know people</item>
        <item>What is success? I think it is a mixture of having a flair for the thing that you are doing; knowing that it is not enough, that you have got to have hard work and a certain sense of purpose</item>
        <item>Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other</item>
        <item>Success is not measured by what you accomplish, but by the opposition you have encountered, and the courage with which you have maintained the struggle against overwhelming odds</item>
        <item>Success or failure depends more upon attitude than upon capacity successful men act as though they have accomplished or are enjoying something. Soon it becomes a reality. Act, look, feel successful, conduct yourself accordingly, and you will be amazed at the positive results</item>
        <item>The greatest sign of success for a teacher&#8230; is to be able to say, \'The children are now working as if I did not exist</item>
        <item>You don\'t have to be a genius or a visionary or even a college graduate to be successful. You just need a framework and a dream</item>
        <item>I don\'t know the key to success, but the key to failure is trying to please everybody.</item>
        <item>The most important single ingredient in the formula of success is knowing how to get along with people</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Positive">
        <item>Find a place inside where there\'s joy, and the joy will burn out the pain</item>
        <item>Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see a shadow</item>
        <item>No matter what you\'re going through, there\'s a light at the end of the tunnel and it may seem hard to get to it but you can do it and just keep working towards it and you\'ll find the positive side of things</item>
        <item>Positive anything is better than negative nothing</item>
        <item>Yesterday is not ours to recover, but tomorrow is ours to win or lose</item>
        <item>You\'re going to go through tough times - that\'s life. But I say, \'Nothing happens to you, it happens for you.\' See the positive in negative events</item>
        <item>If you have a positive attitude and constantly strive to give your best effort, eventually you will overcome your immediate problems and find you are ready for greater challenges</item>
        <item>Believe that life is worth living and your belief will help create the fact</item>
        <item>I believe if you keep your faith, you keep your trust, you keep the right attitude, if you\'re grateful, you\'ll see God open up new doors</item>
        <item>Work hard for what you want because it won\'t come to you without a fight. You have to be strong and courageous and know that you can do anything you put your mind to. If somebody puts you down or criticizes you, just keep on believing in yourself and turn it into something positive</item>
        <item>Once you replace negative thoughts with positive ones, you\'ll start having positive results</item>
        <item>Find a place inside where there\'s joy, and the joy will burn out the pain</item>
        <item>I truly believe that everything that we do and everyone that we meet is put in our path for a purpose. There are no accidents; we\'re all teachers - if we\'re willing to pay attention to the lessons we learn, trust our positive instincts and not be afraid to take risks or wait for some miracle to come knocking at our door</item>
        <item>Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see a shadow.</item>
        <item>No matter what you\'re going through, there\'s a light at the end of the tunnel and it may seem hard to get to it but you can do it and just keep working towards it and you\'ll find the positive side of things</item>
        <item>Positive anything is better than negative nothing</item>
        <item>Yesterday is not ours to recover, but tomorrow is ours to win or lose.</item>
        <item>You\'re going to go through tough times - that\'s life. But I say, \'Nothing happens to you, it happens for you.\' See the positive in negative events.</item>
        <item>If you have a positive attitude and constantly strive to give your best effort, eventually you will overcome your immediate problems and find you are ready for greater challenges.</item>
        <item>Believe that life is worth living and your belief will help create the fact</item>
        <item>Did I offer peace today? Did I bring a smile to someone\'s face? Did I say words of healing? Did I let go of my anger and resentment? Did I forgive? Did I love? These are the real questions. I must trust that the little bit of love that I sow now will bear many fruits, here in this world and the life to come.</item>
        <item>I believe if you keep your faith, you keep your trust, you keep the right attitude, if you\'re grateful, you\'ll see God open up new doors</item>
        <item>Your attitude is like a box of crayons that color your world. Constantly color your picture gray, and your picture will always be bleak. Try adding some bright colors to the picture by including humor, and your picture begins to lighten up.</item>
        <item>You\'ve done it before and you can do it now. See the positive possibilities. Redirect the substantial energy of your frustration and turn it into positive, effective, unstoppable determination.</item>
        <item>You cannot have a positive life and a negative mind</item>
        <item>Always Do Your Best. Your best is going to change from moment to moment; it will be different when you are healthy as opposed to sick. Under any circumstance, simply do your best, and you will avoid self-judgment, self-abuse and regret</item>
        <item>If you\'re not making mistakes, then you\'re not doing anything. I\'m positive that a doer makes mistakes</item>
        <item>Correction does much, but encouragement does more</item>
        <item>Positive thinking will let you do everything better than negative thinking will</item>
        <item>I always like to look on the optimistic side of life, but I am realistic enough to know that life is a complex matter</item>
        <item>In order to carry a positive action we must develop here a positive vision.</item>
        <item>The most important thing is to try and inspire people so that they can be great in whatever they want to do</item>
        <item>he joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun</item>
        <item>Few things in the world are more powerful than a positive push. A smile. A world of optimism and hope. A \'you can do it\' when things are tough</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Leadership">
        <item>If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader</item>
        <item>A leader is one who knows the way, goes the way, and shows the ways</item>
        <item>It is better to lead from behind and to put others in front, especially when you celebrate victory when nice things occur. You take the front line when there is danger. Then people will appreciate your leadership.</item>
        <item>Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower</item>
        <item>A good leader takes a little more than his share of the blame, a little less than his share of the credit</item>
        <item>Don\'t find fault, find a remedy</item>
        <item>Be a yardstick of quality. Some people aren\'t used to an environment where excellence is expected</item>
        <item>Lead, follow, or get out of the way</item>
        <item>Management is doing things right; leadership is doing the right things</item>
        <item>A leader is best when people barely know he exists, when his work is done, his aim fulfilled, they will say: we did it ourselves</item>
        <item>If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader</item>
        <item>A leader is one who knows the way, goes the way, and shows the way</item>
        <item>It is better to lead from behind and to put others in front, especially when you celebrate victory when nice things occur. You take the front line when there is danger. Then people will appreciate your leadership</item>
        <item>Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower</item>
        <item>A good leader takes a little more than his share of the blame, a little less than his share of the credit</item>
        <item>Don\'t find fault, find a remedy</item>
        <item>Leadership is solving problems. The day soldiers stop bringing you their problems is the day you have stopped leading them. They have either lost confidence that you can help or concluded you do not care. Either case is a failure of leadership</item>
        <item>Be a yardstick of quality. Some people aren\'t used to an environment where excellence is expected</item>
        <item>Lead, follow, or get out of the way</item>
        <item>Management is doing things right; leadership is doing the right things</item>
        <item>A leader is best when people barely know he exists, when his work is done, his aim fulfilled, they will say: we did it ourselves</item>
        <item>Leadership - leadership is about taking responsibility, not making excuses.</item>
        <item>If you think you can do a thing or think you can\'t do a thing, you\'re right</item>
        <item>Outstanding leaders go out of their way to boost the self-esteem of their personnel. If people believe in themselves, it\'s amazing what they can accomplish</item>
        <item>Leadership and learning are indispensable to each other.</item>
        <item>Enlightened leadership is spiritual if we understand spirituality not as some kind of religious dogma or ideology but as the domain of awareness where we experience values like truth, goodness, beauty, love and compassion, and also intuition, creativity, insight and focused attention</item>
        <item>Leadership is the capacity to translate vision into reality</item>
        <item>A genuine leader is not a searcher for consensus but a molder of consensus</item>
        <item>When you can\'t make them see the light, make them feel the heat</item>
        <item>The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves.</item>
        <item>I suppose leadership at one time meant muscles; but today it means getting along with people</item>
        <item>People ask the difference between a leader and a boss. The leader leads, and the boss drives</item>
        <item>High expectations are the key to everything</item>
        <item>Leadership is the art of getting someone else to do something you want done because he wants to do it</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Life">
        <item>Throughout life people will make you mad, disrespect you and treat you bad. Let God deal with the things they do, cause hate in your heart will consume you too</item>
        <item>Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment</item>
        <item>If you live long enough, you\'ll make mistakes. But if you learn from them, you\'ll be a better person. It\'s how you handle adversity, not how it affects you. The main thing is never quit, never quit, never quit</item>
        <item>Life is a song - sing it. Life is a game - play it. Life is a challenge - meet it. Life is a dream - realize it. Life is a sacrifice - offer it. Life is love - enjoy it</item>
        <item>The privilege of a lifetime is being who you are</item>
        <item>The truth is you don\'t know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed</item>
        <item>Throughout life people will make you mad, disrespect you and treat you bad. Let God deal with the things they do, cause hate in your heart will consume you too</item>
        <item>Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment</item>
        <item>If you live long enough, you\'ll make mistakes. But if you learn from them, you\'ll be a better person. It\'s how you handle adversity, not how it affects you. The main thing is never quit, never quit, never quit</item>
        <item>Life is a song - sing it. Life is a game - play it. Life is a challenge - meet it. Life is a dream - realize it. Life is a sacrifice - offer it. Life is love - enjoy it</item>
        <item>The privilege of a lifetime is being who you are</item>
        <item>Kindness, I\'ve discovered, is everything in life</item>
        <item>Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you\'re living?</item>
        <item>The true secret of happiness lies in taking a genuine interest in all the details of daily life</item>
        <item>Life is a series of natural and spontaneous changes. Don\'t resist them - that only creates sorrow. Let reality be reality. Let things flow naturally forward in whatever way they like</item>
        <item>One way to get the most out of life is to look upon it as an adventure</item>
        <item>The hardest years in life are those between ten and seventy.</item>
        <item>Life itself is the most wonderful fairy tale</item>
        <item>I have a simple philosophy: Fill what\'s empty. Empty what\'s full. Scratch where it itches</item>
        <item>Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one\'s definition of your life; define yourself.</item>
        <item>This life, which had been the tomb of his virtue and of his honour, is but a walking shadow; a poor player, that struts and frets his hour upon the stage, and then is heard no more: it is a tale told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, signifying nothing.</item>
        <item>A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life</item>
        <item>Our life always expresses the result of our dominant thoughts</item>
        <item>If you love life, don\'t waste time, for time is what life is made up of.</item>
        <item>You will never be happy if you continue to search for what happiness consists of. You will never live if you are looking for the meaning of life</item>
        <item>How far you go in life depends on your being tender with the young, compassionate with the aged, sympathetic with the striving and tolerant of the weak and strong. Because someday in your life you will have been all of these</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Education">
        <item>Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world</item>
        <item>Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself</item>
        <item>The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet.</item>
        <item>Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom.</item>
        <item>It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it</item>
        <item>My mother said I must always be intolerant of ignorance but understanding of illiteracy. That some people, unable to go to school, were more educated and more intelligent than college professors</item>
        <item>The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows.</item>
        <item>An investment in knowledge pays the best interest</item>
        <item>The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change</item>
        <item>Education is the movement from darkness to light</item>
        <item>Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world.</item>
        <item>Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself</item>
        <item>The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet.</item>
        <item>Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom.</item>
        <item>It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it</item>
        <item>My mother said I must always be intolerant of ignorance but understanding of illiteracy. That some people, unable to go to school, were more educated and more intelligent than college professors</item>
        <item>The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows</item>
        <item>An investment in knowledge pays the best interest.</item>
        <item>The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change</item>
        <item>Education is the movement from darkness to light</item>
        <item>The direction in which education starts a man will determine his future in life</item>
        <item>The philosophy of the school room in one generation will be the philosophy of government in the next</item>
        <item>Education is learning what you didn\'t even know you didn\'t know.</item>
        <item>You are always a student, never a master. You have to keep moving forward.</item>
        <item>A man who has never gone to school may steal from a freight car; but if he has a university education, he may steal the whole railroad </item>
        <item>Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught</item>
        <item>Education is the best friend. An educated person is respected everywhere. Education beats the beauty and the youth.</item>
        <item>Develop a passion for learning. If you do, you will never cease to grow</item>
        <item>Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire.</item>
        <item>If I were again beginning my studies, I would follow the advice of Plato and start with mathematics.</item>
        <item>He who opens a school door, closes a prison</item>
        <item>An education isn\'t how much you have committed to memory, or even how much you know. It\'s being able to differentiate between what you know and what you don\'t</item>
        <item>In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards</item>
        <item>The most influential of all educational factors is the conversation in a child\'s home</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Smile">
        <item>Don\'t cry because it\'s over. Smile because it happened</item>
        <item>A warm smile is the universal language of kindness.</item>
        <item>Too often we underestimate the power of a touch, a smile, a kind word, a listening ear, an honest compliment, or the smallest act of caring, all of which have the potential to turn a life around.</item>
        <item>Let my soul smile through my heart and my heart smile through my eyes, that I may scatter rich smiles in sad hearts.</item>
        <item>A smile is a curve that sets everything straight</item>
        <item>We shall never know all the good that a simple smile can do.</item>
        <item>A smile is the light in your window that tells others that there is a caring, sharing person inside.</item>
        <item>The real man smiles in trouble, gathers strength from distress, and grows brave by reflection</item>
        <item>Smiling is definitely one of the best beauty remedies. If you have a good sense of humor and a good approach to life, that\'s beautiful</item>
        <item>Smile, it\'s free therapy</item>
        <item>Don\'t cry because it\'s over. Smile because it happened</item>
        <item>A warm smile is the universal language of kindness</item>
        <item>Too often we underestimate the power of a touch, a smile, a kind word, a listening ear, an honest compliment, or the smallest act of caring, all of which have the potential to turn a life around</item>
        <item>Let my soul smile through my heart and my heart smile through my eyes, that I may scatter rich smiles in sad hearts.</item>
        <item>A smile is a curve that sets everything straight</item>
        <item>We shall never know all the good that a simple smile can do</item>
        <item>A smile is the light in your window that tells others that there is a caring, sharing person inside</item>
        <item>he real man smiles in trouble, gathers strength from distress, and grows brave by reflection</item>
        <item>Smiling is definitely one of the best beauty remedies. If you have a good sense of humor and a good approach to life, that\'s beautiful</item>
        <item>A smile is happiness you\'ll find right under your nose</item>
        <item>After every storm the sun will smile; for every problem there is a solution, and the soul\'s indefeasible duty is to be of good cheer.</item>
        <item>Remember even though the outside world might be raining, if you keep on smiling the sun will soon show its face and smile back at you</item>
        <item>If you smile when no one else is around, you really mean it.</item>
        <item>Always keep your smile. That\'s how I explain my long life</item>
        <item>Smile in the mirror. Do that every morning and you\'ll start to see a big difference in your life.</item>
        <item>Look back, and smile on perils past</item>
        <item>I think that anybody that smiles automatically looks better.</item>
        <item>A gentle word, a kind look, a good-natured smile can work wonders and accomplish miracles.</item>
        <item>When I look out at the people and they look at me and they\'re smiling, then I know that I\'m loved. That is the time when I have no worries, no problems</item>
        <item>Colours are the smiles of nature</item>
        <item>Wear a smile and have friends; wear a scowl and have wrinkles.</item>
        <item>What sunshine is to flowers, smiles are to humanity. These are but trifles, to be sure; but scattered along life\'s pathway, the good they do is inconceivable</item>
        <item>Be thou the rainbow in the storms of life. The evening beam that smiles the clouds away, and tints tomorrow with prophetic ray</item>
        <item>A smile is the universal welcome</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Wisdom">
        <item>The more you like yourself, the less you are like anyone else, which makes you unique</item>
        <item>It\'s not what you look at that matters, it\'s what you see.</item>
        <item>For beautiful eyes, look for the good in others; for beautiful lips, speak only words of kindness; and for poise, walk with the knowledge that you are never alone</item>
        <item>Do not go where the path may lead, go instead where there is no path and leave a trail</item>
        <item>The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing</item>
        <item>Discipline is the bridge between goals and accomplishment</item>
        <item>A man must be big enough to admit his mistakes, smart enough to profit from them, and strong enough to correct them</item>
        <item>The pessimist complains about the wind; the optimist expects it to change; the realist adjusts the sails</item>
        <item>A day of worry is more exhausting than a week of work</item>
        <item>Be happy. It\'s one way of being wise.</item>
        <item>The more you like yourself, the less you are like anyone else, which makes you unique.</item>
        <item>It\'s not what you look at that matters, it\'s what you see.</item>
        <item>For beautiful eyes, look for the good in others; for beautiful lips, speak only words of kindness; and for poise, walk with the knowledge that you are never alone</item>
        <item>Do not go where the path may lead, go instead where there is no path and leave a trail</item>
        <item>The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing.</item>
        <item>If you\'re trying to achieve, there will be roadblocks. I\'ve had them; everybody has had them. But obstacles don\'t have to stop you. If you run into a wall, don\'t turn around and give up. Figure out how to climb it, go through it, or work around it</item>
        <item>Discipline is the bridge between goals and accomplishment</item>
        <item>A man must be big enough to admit his mistakes, smart enough to profit from them, and strong enough to correct them.</item>
        <item>The pessimist complains about the wind; the optimist expects it to change; the realist adjusts the sails.</item>
        <item>A day of worry is more exhausting than a week of work</item>
        <item>Be happy. It\'s one way of being wise</item>
        <item>Beware of false knowledge; it is more dangerous than ignorance.</item>
        <item>People spend too much time finding other people to blame, too much energy finding excuses for not being what they are capable of being, and not enough energy putting themselves on the line, growing out of the past, and getting on with their lives.</item>
        <item>Everything that irritates us about others can lead us to an understanding of ourselves.</item>
        <item>By three methods we may learn wisdom: First, by reflection, which is noblest; Second, by imitation, which is easiest; and third by experience, which is the bitterest.</item>
        <item>When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don\'t adjust the goals, adjust the action steps</item>
        <item>We are what our thoughts have made us; so take care about what you think. Words are secondary. Thoughts live; they travel far</item>
        <item>Never let your head hang down. Never give up and sit down and grieve. Find another way. And don\'t pray when it rains if you don\'t pray when the sun shines.</item>
        <item>My father said there were two kinds of people in the world: givers and takers. The takers may eat better, but the givers sleep better</item>
        <item>Experience is not what happens to you; it\'s what you do with what happens to you.</item>
        <item>Everything comes to us that belongs to us if we create the capacity to receive it</item>
        <item>Knowledge comes, but wisdom lingers. It may not be difficult to store up in the mind a vast quantity of facts within a comparatively short time, but the ability to form judgments requires the severe discipline of hard work and the tempering heat of experience and maturity</item>
        <item>If you talk to a man in a language he understands, that goes to his head. If you talk to him in his language, that goes to his heart.</item>
        <item>A good head and a good heart are always a formidable combination..</item>
        <item>Wisdom begins in wonder&#8230;</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Change">
        <item>Change is the law of life. And those who look only to the past or present are certain to miss the future</item>
        <item>Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time. We are the ones we\'ve been waiting for. We are the change that we seek.</item>
        <item>If there is no struggle, there is no progress.</item>
        <item>You must be the change you wish to see in the world.</item>
        <item>Never believe that a few caring people can\'t change the world. For, indeed, that\'s all who ever have.</item>
        <item>You must take personal responsibility. You cannot change the circumstances, the seasons, or the wind, but you can change yourself. That is something you have charge of</item>
        <item>The only way to make sense out of change is to plunge into it, move with it, and join the dance</item>
        <item>If you don\'t like something, change it. If you can\'t change it, change your attitude.</item>
        <item>When we are no longer able to change a situation - we are challenged to change ourselves</item>
        <item>Progress is impossible without change, and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything.</item>
        <item>Change is the law of life. And those who look only to the past or present are certain to miss the future</item>
        <item>Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time. We are the ones we\'ve been waiting for. We are the change that we seek</item>
        <item>If there is no struggle, there is no progress</item>
        <item>You must be the change you wish to see in the world.</item>
        <item>For the past 33 years, I have looked in the mirror every morning and asked myself: \'If today were the last day of my life, would I want to do what I am about to do today?\' And whenever the answer has been \'No\' for too many days in a row, I know I need to change something.</item>
        <item>Never believe that a few caring people can\'t change the world. For, indeed, that\'s all who ever have.</item>
        <item>You must take personal responsibility. You cannot change the circumstances, the seasons, or the wind, but you can change yourself. That is something you have charge of.</item>
        <item>The only way to make sense out of change is to plunge into it, move with it, and join the dance.</item>
        <item>If you don\'t like something, change it. If you can\'t change it, change your attitude..</item>
        <item>When we are no longer able to change a situation - we are challenged to change ourselves.</item>
        <item>To improve is to change; to be perfect is to change often</item>
        <item>I hope everyone that is reading this is having a really good day. And if you are not, just know that in every new minute that passes you have an opportunity to change that</item>
        <item>If you do not change direction, you may end up where you are heading..</item>
        <item>The first step toward change is awareness. The second step is acceptance</item>
        <item>It may be hard for an egg to turn into a bird: it would be a jolly sight harder for it to learn to fly while remaining an egg. We are like eggs at present. And you cannot go on indefinitely being just an ordinary, decent egg. We must be hatched or go bad</item>
        <item>Sometimes it\'s the smallest decisions that can change your life forever</item>
        <item>If you change the way you look at things, the things you look at change.</item>
        <item>They always say time changes things, but you actually have to change them yourself..</item>
        <item>God grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change, the courage to change the things I can, and the wisdom to know the difference</item>
        <item>Change does not roll in on the wheels of inevitability, but comes through continuous struggle. And so we must straighten our backs and work for our freedom. A man can\'t ride you unless your back is bent.</item>
        <item>Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself</item>
        <item>My friends, love is better than anger. Hope is better than fear. Optimism is better than despair. So let us be loving, hopeful and optimistic. And we\'ll change the world.</item>
        <item>Just when I think I have learned the way to live, life changes</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>